[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":2219,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":6587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure that  when we  combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":1381,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":7969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":11758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":19729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1349,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":21080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3- 0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["6","5"],"rt":4422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":25503,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2006,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":27511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your resu lt.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3509,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":31020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1170,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":32191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4127,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":36319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 becaus e 1 + 1  = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1098,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":37418,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3685,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":41104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":966,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":42071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first numbe r, and t hen add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3265,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":45337,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1069,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":46407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2829,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":49237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":978,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":50216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":53191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":871,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":54063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2639,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":56703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":948,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":57652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get you r result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":60508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":801,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":61311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":16342,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":77655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":34875,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":112531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5978,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":118510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":958,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":119469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2740,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":122210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":956,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":123168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</su b>? <br  /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2529,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":125698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":831,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":126530,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2616,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":129147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":868,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":130016,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5730,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":135747,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3540,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":139288,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":8877,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":148166,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a gener ator und er +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":38179,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":186346,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["Yes","No"],"rt":29045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":215392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":990,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":216383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a  generato r under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":8125,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":224509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":6337,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":230847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a ge nerator  is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":12128,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":242976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2421,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":245399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":250608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1036,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":251645,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10170,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":261816,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3570,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":265387,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1100,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":266487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2987,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":269475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8836,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":278312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":281687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["00","0"],"rt":9063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":290751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":297840,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.12-0 "},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4+1 is 5 which is smaller than 9 so you leave it alone","response_history":["4+1 is 5 which is smaller than 9 so you leave it alone"],"rt":18658,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":316499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4 is 12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 9 and the answer is 3","response_history":["the answer is 12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 4","8 12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 4","8+ 12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 4","8+4 12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 4","8+4  12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 4","8+4 i 12 which is larger than 9 so  you sub tract 4","8+4 is 12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 4","8+4 is 12 which is larger than 9 so you subtract 9 and the answer is 3"],"rt":38540,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":355040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"the identity is 0 because combined with 9 it gives 9","response_history":["the identity is 0 bev","the identity is 0 because combined with 9 it gives 9"],"rt":25078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":380121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":387161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":5607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":392769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["9","0"],"rt":10160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":402930,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4668,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":407599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is  2 a gene rator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure how generators work","response_history":["I'm not sure how generators work"],"rt":58454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":466054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I would say yes because it is a multiple of 9","response_history":["I would say yes because it is a multiple of 9"],"rt":13704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":479760,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"possibly,  but I'm  not sure how generators work","response_history":["possibly, but I'm not sure how generators work"],"rt":9927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":489688,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think so but I'm not sure","response_history":["I think so but I'm not sure"],"rt":7246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":496935,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":20918,"trial_type":"instruc tions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":517855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+n-2","response_history":["+n-2"],"rt":47344,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":565200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x=+n-2. I have no idea I'm just guessing","response_history":["x=2-","x=2","x=+n-2. I have no idea I'm just guessing"],"rt":43114,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":608315,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a ge nerator  under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure I don't understand generators","response_history":["I'm not sure i ","I'm not sure i","I'm not sure I f","I'm not sure I don't understand generators"],"rt":31754,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":640071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3845,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":643919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"Fa lse","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4649,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":648569,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6647,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":655217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"No idea just guessing. this is over my head","response_history":["No idea hs","No idea h","No idea just guessn","No idea just guessub","No idea just gue ssu","No  idea just guessing ","No idea just guessing. this is over my head"],"rt":16989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":672208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":14436,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":686645,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"not sure, don't understand","response_history":["not sure, don't understan d"],"rt":7466,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":694112,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":3438,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":697552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1078,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":698631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","response_history":["32"],"rt":2367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":700999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3474,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":704474,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"algebra I think","response_history":["algebra I think"],"rt":7844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":712320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":2576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":714896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":1688,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":716585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":719745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":722729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2343,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":725073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1653,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":726727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["Englihs","Englih","English"],"rt":6480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":733208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen  and pape r at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3055,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":736264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I understood the first part but didn't get the generator or +n stuff. needs more explanation.","response_history":["I understood the fist","I understood the fis","I understood the fi","I understood the first part but didn't get the genr","I understood the first part but didn't get the generator or +n stuff. needs more explanation."],"rt":28320,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":764585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]